turnkeyinternet.net 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy

  * **_Pssst..._** Start making money with the cloud today with our **Cloud Reseller** platform.
  *  __Home/
  * Policies/
  *  **Privacy**
  * / __

Turnkey Internet's online privacy policy governs personal information gathered on our Internet and affiliates sites. 

#### Our Commitment to Online Security

Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. Billing information is encrypted whenever transmitted or received online. Personal information is accessible only by staff or volunteers designated to handle online complaints or requests. All Turnkey Internet agents and contractors with access to personal information obtained on the Turnkey Internet web sites are also bound to adhere to this policy.

#### Personal Information that Turnkey Internet May Collect Online

Turnkey Internet collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone, IP (internet protocol) and facsimile numbers, billing information, and any necessary customer service information. Turnkey Internet may also collect business information from Agents and Resellers of our products and services which could constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity.

Turnkey Internet does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our sites are structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

#### Turnkey Internet Uses Personal Information Collected Online

Unless you consent, we will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries, handle complaints, provide operational notices and in program record-keeping. We also process billing and business requests related to program participation. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a list to receive information about other Turnkey Internet products and services. This election box only appears in places where the department collecting personal information maintains such lists. At any time you can add or remove your name from a Turnkey Internet list by contacting us.

#### How Your Information May Be Shared

In order to provide quality customer service, Turnkey Internet may refer inquiries to our agents. For example, in providing a domain name registration, we may need to provide a 3rd party agent with the information necessary to register said domain name on your behalf.

**We never sell or rent your personal information.**

Turnkey Internet may also release personal information to appropriate governmental authorities under the following circumstances: 

  * Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or is requested by a government agency conducting investigations or proceedings;
  * Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
  * Where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

TurnKey Internet employs multiple layers of security, verification and fraud protection - these are normal and customary procedures we employ to protect our clients from potential fraud. TurnKey Internet may send non-identifying data as encrypted and encoded markers to 3rd party verification systems, that may be utilized and stored by 3rd party verification systems. 

#### Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate

You have complete access to your personal information. If your personal information changes, or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please e-mail us with the new information or your review request by contacting us. Let us also know the service program that led to your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.

#### Computer Tracking and Cookies

Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not expressly entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others; but again, these statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Turnkey Internet uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use the Turnkey Internet sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine, and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.

#### EU-U.S. Privacy Shield

TurnKey Internet complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. TurnKey Internet has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, visit [www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, TurnKey Internet is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, TurnKey Internet commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information and HR data. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact TurnKey Internet at: 

TurnKey Internet   
175 Old Loudon Rd  
Latham, N.Y. 12110  

TurnKey Internet has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint. The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you. TurnKey Internet complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

#### GDPR Readiness

TurnKey Internet complies with all recommendations and guidelines set forth by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) legislation introduced by the European Union (EU). The purpose of the legislation is to regulate data protection as well as provide users with better transparency and control over their personal data. For more information regarding GDPR, visit [http://www.eugdpr.org](http://www.eugdpr.org/)

If you choose to subscribe to any TurnKey Internet services, the information you supply on our order forms will be stored within our billing system in a secured fashion, and will be kept for as long as necessary to provide you with the requested services, or to comply with state/federal requirements. However, if you no longer wish to have your information stored in our billing or CRM systems, please contact us with a removal request.

If you contact us, and feel we have not addressed your privacy questions or concerns adequately, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection authority directly.

Individuals have access to personal information about them that an organization holds and be able to correct, amend, or delete that information where it is inaccurate, or has been processed in violation of the Principles, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the individual's privacy in the case in question, or where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated. This information can be reviewed and corrected within your client area.

Your personal information will not be supplied to any third parties.

You will be notified of any changes to this policy via the email address on file in our billing system.

##### Problems or Complaints with our Privacy Policy

If you have a complaint about Turnkey Internet compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us.

Last Revised on May 24th, 2018
